VPCs are closely related to IP networks.
VPC 与 IP 网络密切相关
In order to set up a VPC,
为了建立一个 VPC
we need to provide it a network range.
我们需要提供一个网络范围
Let's look briefly at what a network range is.
让我们简单来看一下网络的范围是什么
A network range is a consecutive set of IP addresses.
网络范围是连续的一组 IP 地址
In order to more concisely describe a network range,
为了更简洁地描述一个网络范围
AWS uses CIDR notation.
AWS 使用 CIDR 表示法
CIDR is an acronym for Classless Inter-Domain Routing,
CIDR 是无类域间路由的首字母缩写词
but we don't really need to worry about what all that means.
但我们不需要担心这意味着什么
CIDR notation is comprised of an IP address,
CIDR 表示法由 IP 地址组成
followed by a slash, followed by a number.
后跟一个斜杠 后跟一个数字
The IP address is the first address in the network range.
IP 地址是网络范围内的第一个地址
The number after the slash tells us how big the range is.
斜杠后的数字告诉我们的范围有多大
The smaller the number,
数字越小
the more addresses in the network range.
网络范围内的地址越多
Well, technically we can use any number between zero and 32.
严格来说 我们可以使用零到 32之间的任何数字
If we stick to 16 or 24,
如果我们坚持 16 或 24
things stay a lot simpler.
事情就更简单了
If we use /16,
如果我们用 /16
we use the maximum of the second half of the IP address as the end of the network range.
我们将 IP 地址的后半部分的最大值用作网络范围的末尾
So 10.2.0.0/16 goes from
所以 10.2.0.0/ 16 从
10.2.0.0 to 10.2.245.255.
10.2.0.0 10.2.0.0 到 10.2.245.255
If we use a slash 24,
如果我们用 24
we use the maximum of the last quarter of the IP or
我们使用最后一个季度的 IP 或
10.2.0.0/24 would go
10.2.0.0/ 10.2.0.0/ 24
from 10.2.0.0 to 10.2.0.255.
从 10.2.0.0 到 10.2.0.255
The detailed mechanics of using CIDR notation to determine
使用 CIDR 表示法确定
a network range involve a topic called bit masking.
网络范围涉及称为位掩码的主题
That goes beyond the scope of this course.
这超出了本课程的范围
For now, you can just remember that /24 means
现在你还记得 /24 的意思
255 addresses and /16 means 65,000 addresses.
255 个地址和 /16 表示 65000 个地址
You may have run into situations where two computers on a network
您可能已运行到网络上的两台计算机
try to use the same IP address, things don't go well.
尝试使用相同的 IP 地址 情况不太顺利
They fight and complain, and no one is happy.
他们打架 抱怨 没有人高兴
When two VPCs have overlapping network ranges,
当两个 VPC 有重叠的网络范围时
the concept is basically the same.
这个概念基本上是一样的
You cannot connect two VPCs that have the same or overlapping network ranges.
不能连接两个具有相同或重叠网络范围的 VPC